Guide to Tuli Kupferberg and Sylvia Topp Papers MSS.385
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI. Research and Source Material, 1821-2010; 1960-1995; 70 Linear Feet in 50 record cartons, 23 manuscript boxes, 1 flat folder, 2 flat boxes, 5 oversize flat boxes
  - Subseries A. Research and Subject files, 1821-2010; 1960-1995; 52 Linear Feet in 50 record cartons, 1 flat box, 1 flat folder, 2 oversize flat boxes
    - Work Secondaries, 1932-1967 (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - Work: The Job Itself, 1976-1978 (Box 94, Folder 28)
    - Workers, 1970-1972 (Box 94, Folder 29)
    - Workers and Left, undated (Box 94, Folder 30)
    - Working, 1967-1969 (Box 94, Folder 31)
    - Workplace Violence, 1959-1989 (Box 94, Folder 32-33)
    - World's Worst Sex, 1963-1982 (Box 94, Folder 34)
    - Worst Books List, 1969-1973 (Box 94, Folder 35)
    - Writers and Publishing, 1941-1980 (Box 94, Folder 36-37)
    - Writers Lives, 1930s, 1960-1963, undated (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Writing, 1960-1963 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Writing Articles and Advertisements, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Writing as a Disease, 1995 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Writing in America, 1940, 1972-1981 (Box 95, Folder 5-6)
    - Writing Life, 1962-1985 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Writing Proverbs, 1962-1978 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Writing Research, 1958-1985 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Writing Technique Quotations, undated (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Wuppertal, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - WWII Museum, 2007 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Xerox, 1987-1990 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Xian Communism, undated (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - X-mas, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - X-mas / New Years, 1962, undated (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - X-mas -- Old, 1972-1975 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Yellow Book Illustrated, 1939 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Yellow Pages, 1997, undated (Box 95, Folder 19-20)
    - Yeltsin Obituary -- The Nation, 2007 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Yes (Journal), undated (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Young Hegelianism, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - The Young Hegelians -- McLellan, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - The Young Hegelians -- William J. Brazill, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Youth and Art, undated (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - Youth Violence Prevention, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - Zappa Fan Page Interview, 2007 (Box 95, Folder 28)
    - General, 1859-2009 (Box 95, Folder 29-34, Box 96, Folder 1-17, Box 97, Folder 1-16, Box 98, Box 99, Folder 1-18, Box 100, Box 101, Folder 1-12, Box 209, Folder 1-13, Box 146, Folder 6, Box 264, Folder 13, Box 327, Folder 2)
    - General Posters, Illustrations, Event Announcements, 1842, 1875, 1918, 1920-1930, 1960-2009 (Box 103, Folder 1-9, Box 102, Folder 1-6, Box 40, Box 326, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 4, Box Shared Fales 073, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B. Source Publications, 1863, 1869, 1899-1900, 1923, 1933-2009, undated; 12 Linear Feet in 22 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, 3 oversize boxes
    This series is listed alphabetically.
    This series includes publications used by Kuperferberg and Topp for source material for writings, collages, music, and cartoons. These publications include local New York zines, underground newspapers, small press literary magazines, and international journals. Some publication topics include anarchy, politics, protests, sex, art, and humor. Publication dates range from the mid-1800s to 2009. The majority were published in the 1970s-1990s.
    Duplicate copies as well as issues of publications already held within Bobst Library and the Special Collections Libraries were deaccessioned.
    - @-Wire, 1992 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - 3 Acre Floor, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - 1000 New Jokes, 1935 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - 1917: Journal of the International Bolshevik Tendency, 1987-1996 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - A Draft Proposal for an Anarchist Black Cross Group, circa 1979 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Abolishing the Borders from Below, 2003 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - About Face, 1982 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - The Activist, 1991 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Aesthetic Realism Foundation, 1993, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - After the Fall, undated (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - The Agent, 1980-1987 (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Agit-Pop America, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - A.I.C. Open Channel, 1992 (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Ain't it Time We Got Mad!, 1992 (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Alligator Unite Socialist of America American Liberation League, circa 1966 (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - Alpha Null, 1983 (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - Alternative Media, 1980-1983 (Box 211, Folder 15)
    - Alternative Press Review, 1994-2001 (Box 211, Folder 16)
    - AM Here Books, 1991-1992 (Box 211, Folder 17)
    - American Handgunner, 1986 (Box 211, Folder 18)
    - Amex / Canada, 1973 (Box 211, Folder 19)
    - An Outline of Guild Socialism, undated (Box 211, Folder 20)
    - Anarchist Age Weekly Review, 2001 (Box 211, Folder 21)
    - Anarchist Review, 1977-1980 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Anarchist Song Book, 1986 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Anarchist Yellow Pages, 1999 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Anarcho-Syndicalist Review, 2002-2004 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Anarchy, circa 1979 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Anarchy: A Journal of Desire Armed, 1988-2008 (Box 212, Folder 6-8, Box 213, Folder 1-3, Box 233)
    - Anarchy in the U.K., circa 1994 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Anderson Valley Advertiser, 1995-1996 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Answer Me, 1993 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Anti Shyster, undated (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Anti-Social Jr., 1984 (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Anti Social Man, 1982 (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - Anvil, 1981 (Box 213, Folder 9)
    - Appearances, 1991-1998 (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Apple Pie, 1975 (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - Appleton's Journal, 1869 (Box 213, Folder 12)
    - Art Police, 1988-1989 (Box 213, Folder 13)
    - Artless, 1999 (Box 213, Folder 14)
    - Asia, 1923 (Box 213, Folder 15)
    - Aspects, 1964 (Box 213, Folder 16)
    - Ass: Art Star Scene Mag, circa 2003 (Box 213, Folder 17)
    - Atlantic Anarchist Circle, 1998-1999 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Auroville - The City of Human Unity, 1968 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Babushkin's Digest, 2000 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Bad Newz, undated (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Bayou La Rose, 1993 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Beatnik Dreams, 1982 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Beatniks from Space, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Beet, 1995 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Berglers Balz, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Berkeley Barb, 1967 (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Big Hammer, 1990 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Birth and Life Bookstore's Review Newsletter / Catalog: IMPRINTS, 1984 (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Black Eye, 1988-1990, undated (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Black Flag, 1986 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Black Mask, 1993 (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - The Black Panther, 1991 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - The Blotter, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - Bomb, 1981 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Boneless Boelogna, 1989, undated (Box 214, Folder 14)
    - Boog City, 2002, 2008 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - The Book of Prison Slang, 1993 (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - Boxer, 1997 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - The Boys' Club Record, 1962 (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - A Brave and Beautiful Future ... Could Start Now!, 1982 (Box 214, Folder 17)
    - Breakthrough, 1982 (Box 214, Folder 18)
    - Brick, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 19)
    - Bulletin: Students for a Democratic Society, 1964-1965 (Box 214, Folder 20)
    - Busker's Rag, 1992 (Box 214, Folder 21)
    - Bypass, undated (Box 214, Folder 22)
    - Cabinet, 2004 (Box 214, Folder 23)
    - Campaign to Free Vanunu, 1997 (Box 214, Folder 24)
    - Cancionero Revolucionario, 1947 (Box 214, Folder 25)
    - Capital Times, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 26)
    - Catholic Foam, 1989 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - The Catholic Worker, 1993-2003 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Censorship News, 2000-2001 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Challenge - Vietnam Special, 1968 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Chelsea Clinton News, 1982 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Convention-Related Publications, 1968 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Chicken Little, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Class Action, 1991 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Class War, 1994-1995 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Close HLS, 2006 (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Cometbus, circa 2002 (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Common Sense, 1978 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Common Sense for America, 1987 (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - Communicating Vessels, 2002-2007 (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - Communicomics Collective, 1984 (Box 215, Folder 11)
    - Community Empowerment Project, 2003 (Box 215, Folder 12)
    - Computer State Notes, 1982 (Box 215, Folder 13)
    - Connexions, 1982 (Box 215, Folder 14)
    - Counterpunch, 1994-2001 (Box 215, Folder 15)
    - Control Zone, undated (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Country Gentleman, 1947-1952 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - The Country Home, 1933 (Box 215, Folder 16)
    - Coyote Howls, 1978-1979 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Crapouillot, 1953-1963 (Box 233, Folder 1-6)
    - Crescent International, 1997 (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - Croc, 1986 (Box 215, Folder 17)
    - The Crusader, 1959-1963 (Box 215, Folder 18)
    - Cultural Correspondence, 1977-1985 (Box 215, Folder 19-20)
    - Cultural Democracy, 1984, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Cultural Worker, circa 1974-1976 (Box 216, Folder 2, Box 234, Folder 5)
    - The Cynical Utopian, 2009 (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - Daily World, 1970 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - The DC Gazette, 1980 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - Death, 1978 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - Democratic Left, 1982 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Deolog, 1997 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Dialogue New Orleans' Progressive Community Journal, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - The Digger Papers, undated (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - Dikobraz, 1981 (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Dirt: A Supplement to Sassy, 1991 (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - Dog World, 1956-1957 (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - Dreaming Spires and Flaming Tyres, 1940-2010 (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Drunken Boat, undated (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - Ear Magazine East, 1981, 1986 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - Eat My Shit, 1987 (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - Eclectic Magazine, 1863 (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - Ecomedia, 1991 (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - Elan, 1976-1978 (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - Emancipation, 1983 (Box 216, Folder 15)
    - Encounter, 1967 (Box 216, Folder 16)
    - Endless Struggle, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 17)
    - English Knights, 1963 (Box 216, Folder 18)
    - Erasmus Montanus, 1984 (Box 216, Folder 19)
    - Extra!, 2006 (Box 216, Folder 20)
    - Extranational News, 1997 (Box 216, Folder 21)
    - Extraphile, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 22)
    - Fact Sheet, 1995-1997 (Box 216, Folder 23, Box 217, Folder 1-2)
    - Feasts and Seasons, 1985 (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - Feh!, 1986-1993 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Fish Rapper Digest, 1994 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - Fizz, 2005 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Flower, 1994 (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - Forum: the Journal of Human Relations, 1968 (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - Frank, 1991 (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - Free Society, undated (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - Freedom, 1995-2001 (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - Freedom -- Anarchist Fortnightly, 1999-2002 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - Freedom -- Anarchist News and Views, 2006 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - The Freedom Socialist, 1990 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - Freespace, 1978 (Box 217, Folder 12)
    - Fu Spiegel, 1968 (Box 217, Folder 13)
    - Funny Times, 2002 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - Gadfly, 1999 (Box 217, Folder 14)
    - The Gargoyle, 1982-1983 (Box 217, Folder 15)
    - Global Media: Rights and Wrongs, 1994 (Box 217, Folder 16)
    - Global Outlook, 2004 (Box 217, Folder 17)
    - Green Anarchy, 2000-2003 (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - Green Revolution, 1980 (Box 217, Folder 18)
    - Guerrilla, 1968 (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - Gulf War Notes, 1991 (Box 217, Folder 19)
    - Harbinger, 1983, undated (Box 218, Folder 1, Box 234, Folder 8)
    - Harpoon, 1975 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Harvest Quarterly, 1976-1977 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - Heeb, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - Here and Now, 1986-1987, 1994, undated (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - Heresies, 1980 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - Heterodoxy, 1992 (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - Highlights: The Boys' Club of New York, 1965 (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - Hit Parader, 1948 (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - Hunter / Gatherer, 1960-2010 (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - Ideological Commentary, 1993-1994 (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - Il Peccato, 1990 (Box 234, Folder 9)
    - Impact Press, 2000, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 10)
    - Incite, 1985 (Box 218, Folder 11)
    - Independent Politics News, 2005 (Box 218, Folder 12)
    - Inmates' Voice, 1982 (Box 234, Folder 9)
    - Instead of a Magazine, 1990 (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - It, 1969 (Box 234, Folder 9)
    - Jackpot Years, 1992 (Box 218, Folder 14)
    - The Jewish Radical, 1995-1996 (Box 218, Folder 15)
    - Jews, 1999 (Box 218, Folder 16)
    - Jews for Racial and Economic Justice, 1997 (Box 218, Folder 17)
    - Johnson with Eyes Open, 1964 (Box 218, Folder 18)
    - The Journal of Irreproducible Results, 1968 (Box 218, Folder 19)
    - Judaica Book News, 1983 (Box 218, Folder 20)
    - Jump Cut, 1981 (Box 234, Folder 9)
    - Kick it Over, 1994, 2004 (Box 218, Folder 21, Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Kids Times, 1985 (Box 218, Folder 22)
    - Kooks, 1984 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - Krylon Underground, 1991 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Laughing Maniacs, 1980 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Le Crapouillot, 1973-1974 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Le Rire, 1899
    - Lear's, 1991 (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - Liberation, 1968 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - Libertarian Workers Bulletin, 1982, 1987 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Lies of Our Times, 1992 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - The Linking Ring, 1991, 1993 (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - Lip, 2004 (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - Lithopinion, 1973 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - Lookout!, 1987 (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - Love and Rage, 1995 (Box 219, Folder 12)
    - The LPCR Newsletter, 1982 (Box 219, Folder 13)
    - Lumpen, 1996 (Box 219, Folder 14)
    - Lungfull Magazine, 1998 (Box 219, Folder 15)
    - Lürzer's International Archive, 1997 (Box 219, Folder 16)
    - Lyrical Times, 2003 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - M. gentle men for gender justice, 1984 (Box 219, Folder 17)
    - Mad Magazine, 1966, 1979 (Box 219, Folder 18)
    - The Magazine, 1983 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Magpie, 1961 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - Mainstream, circa 1973 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - Marxachas Lenineachas Padraic O Conaire, undated (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - The Match!, 1991 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - Maximum Rock n Roll, 1984, 2001 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - Mazel-Tov Cocktail, 1995 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - Media Access New York, 1993 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - Meditations, 1983 (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - Memories of a Makhnovist Partisan, 1993 (Box 220, Folder 10)
    - Meshuggah, 1991-1997 (Box 220, Folder 11-12)
    - Michtav-Habiru, 1991 (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - Midnight Notes, 1981-1985 (Box 220, Folder 14)
    - Militarism, circa 1984 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Milk Plant Monthly, 1943 (Box 220, Folder 15)
    - The Mill Hunk Herald, 1981 (Box 220, Folder 16)
    - Minne Ha! Ha!, 1981-1982, 1985 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Missing in Action, circa 1977 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Modern Times, 2000 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Morning Star, 1993 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Movie Life Year Book, 1947-1948 (Box 220, Folder 17, Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Mumbles, 1984 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - The Munsey, 1899-1900, undated (Box 221, Folder 3-4)
    - Munsey's Magazine, undated (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - Munster Book, 2004 (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - My Own Cum, undated (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - National Blabbermouth, 1984 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - National Guardian, 1967 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - National Technical Information Service, 1970 (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - National Weed, 1976 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - The New Censorship: Charles Bukowski, 1991 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - The New Hampshire Gazette, 1991 (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - New Image, circa 1978 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - New Internationalist, 1994 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - New Left Notes, 1967 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - New Liberation News Service, 1992-1993 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - New York Daily Planet, 1976 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - New York Nights, 2003 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - New York Rat!, 2006-2007 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - New York Waste, 2000 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - Newlife, 1997 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - News and Letters, 1993 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - The Newsletter, 1971, 1978 (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper, 1979 (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Newswreck, 1977 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - Nexus, 1997 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - The Nice Paper, 1992 (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - Nightmares of Reason, 1987 (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - No Trees, 1997 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Nonviolent Activist, 1999-2004 (Box 222, Folder 11)
    - Northern Lights, 1963 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - Not Bored!, 1993-1996 (Box 222, Folder 13)
    - The Nothing Issue, 1985 (Box 222, Folder 14)
    - Nucleus, 1994-1995 (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - Nudel Books, 1989, undated (Box 222, Folder 16)
    - Nuestra Poesia, 1984 (Box 222, Folder 17)
    - Nyak-Nyak, undated (Box 222, Folder 18)
    - The Objector, 2002 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Off the Wall Street Journal, 1983 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - OHMTRA, 2000-2004 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - The Ojai Orange / Other Scenes, 1972, 2001, 2006-2007 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - The Oldie, 1993 (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - On the Fiddle, undated (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Only Paper Today, 1976 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - Ooze, 1987 (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - Organise! For Revolutionary Anarchism, 2001-2002 (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - The Other Israel, 1986 (Box 223, Folder 8)
    - Other Scenes, 1980 (Box 223, Folder 9)
    - Our City -- Our Walls, 2004 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Outing, 1898 (Box 223, Folder 10)
    - Overthrow, 1982-1988 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - The Overwhelmer, 2001 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Ocean Ecologist, 1990 (Box 223, Folder 11)
    - Pan Arts, 1984 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Panic, 1986 (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - Pasta Times, 1980-1984 (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - Peace News, 2000, 2003-2004 (Box 223, Folder 14)
    - Peace Work, 2002 (Box 223, Folder 15)
    - Peaceful Beginnings, 1987 (Box 223, Folder 16)
    - PEN American Center Newsletter, 1986 (Box 223, Folder 17)
    - The Penumbra, undated (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - People's Weekly World, 2000, 2005 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Philosophy Now, 2001 (Box 223, Folder 18)
    - Physical Culture, 1936-1937 (Box 223, Folder 19)
    - Pimp Magazine, undated (Box 223, Folder 20)
    - Pink Pages, undated (Box 223, Folder 21)
    - The Plague, 1982 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Planet Crescendo, 1983 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Poetry Book -- Animals -- By Sparrow, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 2)
    - Poetry / Prose Publications, 1971-2008 (Box 224, Folder 3-7, Box 225, Folder 1-2)
    - Poetry Project Newsletter, 1989-2009 (Box 225, Folder 3-4)
    - Political Art Documentation, 1981 (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - Politically Correct, 1993 (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - Post New York Post, 1984 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Primary Documents, 1989-1995 (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - Prisoncamp Reality, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 8)
    - Private Eye, 1962, 1980-1987, 1993-1998, 2002 (Box 225, Folder 9)
    - Processed World, 1981-1989 (Box 225, Folder 10-12)
    - Profane Existence, 1994 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - The Progressive, 1997 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - The Progressive Review, 1988-2004 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - Propaganda, undated (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - P.S. -- Prolifers for Survival, 1983 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Psilist, 1984 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - Public Illumination Magazine, 1980, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Public Press / News Network, 1972 (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - Publish and Perish, 1960-2010 (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - Publishers Union, 1979 (Box 226, Folder 8)
    - Radar, 1981 (Box 226, Folder 9)
    - Radical America, 1971-1984 (Box 226, Folder 10)
    - Radical Cheerleader, circa 2000 (Box 226, Folder 11)
    - Radical Philosophy, 2000-2001 (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - Radical Philosophy Newsletter, 1997-2001 (Box 226, Folder 13)
    - Rag Shock, undated (Box 226, Folder 14)
    - Rain Taxi, 2000-2001 (Box 226, Folder 15)
    - Raise the Stakes, 1988-1993 (Box 226, Folder 16)
    - Rant, 1993, undated (Box 226, Folder 17)
    - Rattlesnake, 2000-2001 (Box 226, Folder 18)
    - A Reader's Guide to the Underground Press, 1999 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - Real America, 1933 (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - The Rebel, 1984 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - Rebel Violence v. Hierarchical Violence, 1986 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - Red and Black Revolution, 1998-1999 (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - Red Balloon Collective, circa 1985 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - Red Bass, 1984 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Red Diaper Baby, 2003 (Box 227, Folder 7)
    - Red Eye on the News, 1990 (Box 227, Folder 8)
    - Red Pepper, 1996 (Box 227, Folder 9)
    - Religion of the Month, 1992 (Box 227, Folder 10)
    - Re/search, 1981 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Responsive Investing News, 1992 (Box 227, Folder 11)
    - Revision, 1988 (Box 227, Folder 12)
    - Revolt!, circa 1999 (Box 227, Folder 13)
    - Revolutionary History, 1988 (Box 227, Folder 14)
    - Richie Bush: The Poor Little Oligarch, 2004 (Box 227, Folder 15)
    - Riff Raff Poets, 1986 (Box 227, Folder 16)
    - Rivista Anarchica, 1982-1992 (Box 227, Folder 17-18)
    - Robert Anton Wilson's Trajectories Newsletter, 1996 (Box 227, Folder 19)
    - The Roc, 1991 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - RohÄÄ, 1981 (Box 227, Folder 20)
    - Roses / Rosas, 1989-1994 (Box 227, Folder 21)
    - Samizdat, 1989 (Box 227, Folder 22)
    - Saturday Night, 1991 (Box 227, Folder 23)
    - SATYA, 2002-2005 (Box 227, Folder 24)
    - Sawblade, 2001 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Scat, 1981 (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - The School Musician, 1931 (Box 228, Folder 2)
    - Semiotext(e) Special, 1980 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Senzapatria, 1987 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - The Shadow, 1980 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Shalom, 1993-2001 (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - The Sheffield Anarchist, 1991 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Ship of Fools, 1991 (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - Sick, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - Sideshow Magazine, 2000-2001 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - SIPAPU, 1983 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - Siren, circa 1972 (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - Small Press Review, 1979-1993 (Box 228, Folder 8)
    - Smile, undated (Box 228, Folder 9)
    - Smoke Signals, 1980-1981 (Box 228, Folder 10)
    - Smurfs in Hell, 1987 (Box 228, Folder 11)
    - Smurna Press Newsletter, undated (Box 228, Folder 12)
    - Snarl, 1988 (Box 228, Folder 13)
    - Social Anarchism, 1980-1997 (Box 228, Folder 14-17)
    - Socialist, 1993 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Socialist Review, 1978 (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Solidarity for Workers' Power, 1968 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Songbooks, 1960-1990, undated (Box 229, Folder 4-5)
    - Songs For Peace, 1993-1997 (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - Sound Collector, circa 1998 (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - Spartacist, 2001 (Box 229, Folder 8)
    - Spectacular Times, 1981, 1988 (Box 229, Folder 9)
    - The Spirit of Freedom, 1989 (Box 229, Folder 10)
    - Sporadical, 1987, 1989, undated (Box 229, Folder 11)
    - Squawk, 1991-1994 (Box 229, Folder 12)
    - Stake, circa 1983 (Box 229, Folder 13)
    - The Stalin School of Falsification Revisited, undated (Box 229, Folder 14)
    - The Stark Fist of Removal, 1983-1999 (Box 229, Folder 15)
    - Stay Free, 2000, 2004 (Box 229, Folder 16)
    - Steamshovel Press, 2003 (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - The Storm, 1978 (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - The Story of the Three Bears, 1993 (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Strike Anywhere, undated (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - Strike Now! -- Huelga Ahora!, undated (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - Struggle, 1991-1999 (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - Students and Youth for the People's Peace / Mayday Collective, undated (Box 230, Folder 6)